<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Colombia Turistica: Guatape</string>
    <string name="Desguatape">Located in eastern Antioquia, it is perhaps the most iconographic municipality in the region. His great stone is the main tourist attraction in town, from there you can enjoy a 360 degrees the lush beauty of the Guatape dam and its neighboring lands, Sockets taxed on the facades of residences and other buildings representing traditions, when the water level low reweighed, you can get to see the dome of the Church of the old Peñol, not counting the stunning scenery and the warmth of its people.</string>
    <string name="Agua">An Unforgettable People Water</string>
    <string name="Autor">Application made by:</string>
    <string name="Autor2">Electronic Engineering Student</string>
    <string name="Bar1">Grill Bar La Playita</string>
    <string name="Bar2">ContraGolpe Sports Bar</string>
    <string name="Bar3">Grill Bar Tierradentro</string>
    <string name="Bares">Bars</string>
    <string name="Demografia">Demographics</string>
    <string name="DesBar1">La Playita is the place to enjoy the scenery of Guatape, an excellent bar and grill in the day and at night !!!</string>
    <string name="DesBar2">It is a resto-bar created for football fans, where they can find great variety of beers and combine them with some delicious chicken wings</string>
    <string name="DesBar3">Restaurant Bar are a typical food where you all find the different foods that characterize our country</string>
    <string name="DesDem">Total Population: 5,279 habitants</string>
    <string name="DesDem10">• Black (0.04%)</string>
    <string name="DesDem2"> • Urban Population: 4,155</string>
    <string name="DesDem3">• Rural Population: 1,124</string>
    <string name="DesDem4">Literacy: 92.3% (2005)</string>
    <string name="DesDem5">• District: 93.8%</string>
    <string name="DesDem6">• Rural areas: 87.8%</string>
    <string name="DesDem7">Ethnography</string>
    <string name="DesDem8">According to figures provided by DANE 2005 census, the Ethnographic composition of the municipality is:</string>
    <string name="DesDem9">• Mestizos and whites (99.96%)</string>
    <string name="DesSitio1">It covers an area of 2,262 hectares and 1,200 million cubic meters, has several marinas and docks where boats are rented and tours are given on tourist boats and marine bike, where you can practice water sports such as kayaking, sailing, water skiing.</string>
    <string name="DesSitio2">It is located 4 km from Guatape, via Peñol, monolith 200 meters high where a 360 degree view is obtained on the Guatape dam impressive.</string>
    <string name="DesSitio3">Where is the church of Our Lady of Carmen Baroque architecture, lined and structured on the roofs of its interior by great bastions and wooden beams making it unique in Antioquia, a large water fountain erected in the square contribute to a greater charm of this park.</string>
    <string name="DesSitio4">Located one block from the main square 1 kmt extension where you can enjoy the most varied cuisine in 25 restaurants found there, with a privileged view over the Guatape dam</string>
    <string name="DesSitio5">It is located on the boardwalk of the Guatape dam is said to be the longest of Antioquia and Colombia for having 600 meters away that goes over the waters of the dam.</string>
    <string name="InfoHote3">Located on the lake Guatapé, it is a magical place surrounded by forests, where you will feel the total connection with nature in a safe and quiet very private atmosphere ...</string>
    <string name="InfoHotel1">Located just 2 km from the entrance to the stone Penol, Hotel Los Recuerdos is the largest and most complete hotel Guatape, enjoys all s services to guarantee you a time of unforgettable rest</string>
    <string name="InfoHotel2">Hotel Isala Guaca is a Paradise near the city of Medellin; pantries located in the sidewalk in front of the dam "El Penol Guatapé". An ideal place for rest, relaxation, where you will find peace and tranquility that has desired</string>
    <string name="SerHotel2">Services: We offer water sports such as fishing boat, kayak, water bike, jetsky, Nautico and sky tour of the reservoir.</string>
    <string name="SerHotel3">Services: Boat transfer to Guatape Hotel and return, Ecological Trekking, Tour in Planchon (Sundays and holidays), evening bonfire on the beach, paddle boats, fishing, beach volleyball court and a game room Pool and Billiards</string>
    <string name="SercHotel1">Services: Wetland: heated pool, Turkish and Jacuzzi,. Restaurant, nightclub. Attractions: Fishing, Motor Worm, Bicycle Nautica, Skiing, Majestic yacht ljo</string>
    <string name="Sitios">Tourist sites</string>
    <string name="TarfHotel1">Rates: Prices per couple per night with 3 meals</string>
    <string name="TarfHotel12">Standard: 300,000 Junior Suite: Imperial Suite 370,000 500,000</string>
    <string name="TarfHotel2">Rates: Prices per person per night with 3 meals</string>
    <string name="TarfHotel22">Shop India: 150,000 Standard: 200.000 Suite: 275,000</string>
    <string name="TarfHotel32">Floating Cabins:  490,000 Cabins BUNGALOW: 390.000 Cabins CHALET: 390,000</string>
    <string name="about">About...</string>
    <string name="descripcion">Best Hotels in Guatape</string>
    <string name="nombre">Hotels</string>
    <string name="sitio1">Guatape Dam</string>
    <string name="sitio2">Peñol Guatape (Piedra del Penol)</string>
    <string name="sitio3">Park Guatape</string>
    <string name="sitio4">Jetty</string>
    <string name="sitio5">Cable Flight</string>
</resources>